Edited at https://subtitletools.com
我认识贝蒂已经有一周了
I had known Betty for a week.
我们每晚都做爱
We screwed every night.
天气预报说有暴风雨
The forecast was for storms.
救到了！
Saved!
是的，现在好好去洗一个澡
Right, time for a nice little shower.
我们初次见面时是在白天
First time we've met in daylight.
你来得太早了
You're much too early.
那又怎么样？我看起来怎么样？
So what? How do I look?
你认为怎么样？
What do you think?
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
你自己吃掉那所有的辣椒
Eating all that chilli by yourself?
在如此炎热的天气下？你疯了
In this heat? You're mad.
无论天气怎样炎热我都会吃辣椒，贝蒂
I'll eat chilli no matter how hot it is, Betty.
我也是！我饿死了
Me too, I'm starving.
见到我高兴吗？
Glad to see me?
他们都是混蛋！
They're all bastards.
谁？
Who?
算了，吻我！
Forget it. Kiss me.
全是混蛋！
All bastards!
难怪女孩和他们分手
No wonder a girl ends up splitting.
等等，解释一下，我不明白你的意思
Wait, explain, I don't get you.
你为什么不注意听我说话？
Why don't you ever listen to me?
我听了，我一直在听！
I do listen. I'm listening.
我不只是只想找一个男人和我做爱
I don't just want a guy to screw me.
想像我在那个乱七八糟的地方消磨了一年...
To think I spent a year in that dump...
...抹擦餐桌，躲避醉汉...
...wiping tables and dodging drunks...
...某天早上我感到再无法忍受上司了
...just to get felt up one morning by the boss.
我现在得重新开始 我太累了. 总之, 我离开了
I've got to start all over again now. I'm dead. Anyway, I left.
甚至买不起一张火车票
Can't even buy a train ticket.
她就像是一支有着透明的蕊喙 和紫红色肤浅的中心的花朵
She was like a flower with translucent antennae and a mauve plastic heart.
没有多少女孩能穿得像她一样随便
Not many girls could dress as casually as she did.
我昨天又看见那个女孩子了
I saw that girl again yesterday.
在如此炎热的天气下，有点不对劲
It's not right, in this fucking heat.
我想她正在寻找你
I think she was looking for you.
不能是你吗, 左格?
Was it you, Zorg?
一个女孩穿着一件小围裙,有着一头乌黑秀发.
A girl in a little apron, with black hair.
像这样的女孩吗?
A girl something like that?
天哪! 岂有此理!
Jesus-fucking-Christ!
是的, 老 乔治, 她是正在找我的.
Yes, old George, she was looking for me.
我该主意了, 我也来.
I've changed my mind, I'm coming too.
你真是走桃花运了
You've torn a page out of Playboy.
-你觉得怎么样? -她挺普通的
-What do you think? -She's a bit common.
那让我恢复信心了
That reassures me.
等一下. 就等一会!
Hold on. Hold on a second!
喝光它
Down in one.
喝光它....
Down in one....
我认为我起不来了，我喝醉了
I don't think I'll be able to get up. I'm drunk.
我得去方便一下
I need to take a piss.
不要压我的膀胱
Don't press on my bladder.
跟你在一起我很高兴
I'm happy being with you.
如果可以的话，我愿意和你呆在一起
I'd like to stay with you if I can.
好的, 我认为你能
Well, I think you can.
我没有老婆, 没有孩子
I've got no wife, no kids.
我们有很好的住所
We've got a nice pad.
我有一个很棒的工作，我是修理工
I have an okay job. I do repairs.
我很有信心，我们还很年青
I'm confident. We're still young.
我不需要解释
I didn't want explanations.
我只想吻她，抚摸她的臀部...
I only wanted to kiss her and caress her ass...
...只要她的膀胱支撑得起
...as long as her bladder held out.
那是谁？醒醒！
Who's that? Wake up!
他是谁？请不必客气，就当是自己家
Who is he? Make yourself at home!
等一下, 我一会就回来
Wait, I'll be right back.
你怎么样? 对不起, 你正坐在我裤子上
How are you? Excuse me, you're sitting on my trousers.
我也不穿内衣裤，穿着感觉不舒服
I don't wear underwear either. It's uncomfortable.
我给你倒些咖啡
I'll get you some coffee.
我得先去煮
I have to make it first.
我去煮吧！你先穿衣服
I'll do it. You get dressed.
是不是因为那个女孩...
Is it because of that girl...
...都到上午十时了，你还躺在床上?
...that you're still in the sack at 10 a.m.?
已经十点了吗?
10:00 already?
有趣的家伙. 现在十一点了
Funny guy. It's 11:00.
她没有让你忘掉吧?
She mustn't make you forget, see?
她没有让你忘掉...
She mustn't make you forget...
...你为什么在这, 为什么我给你房子住， 还付给你工资
...why you're here, why I house you and why I pay you.
我得煮点水
I'll boil some water.
混蛋
Shit!
坦白地说，这一点也不是她的错
This isn't her fault at all, honestly.
在冰箱里，咖啡能更好地保持它的味道
Coffee keeps its flavour better in the fridge.
是的, 你是对的
Yes, you're right.
-来一杯吗? -不, 非常感谢
-Want a shot? -No, thanks very much.
首先要弄湿地面
Always moisten the grounds first.
我只要做一个招聘广告...
All I have to do is to run an ad...
...就会有很多人应聘你做的工作, 但我想要公平一些
...to get loads of guys for your job, but I want to be fair.
我已经雇用你很久了 没有人抱怨过你
I've had you a long time and nobody's ever complained about you.
但我不认为们你留那个女孩在这的同时...
But I don't think you can keep that girl here...
...还能做好工作
...and do your job right.
明白我所说的吗?
Know what I mean?
看到它怎样膨胀了吗?
See how it swells up?
-乔治告诉你关于她的事了吗? -你没有藏住她.
-George told you about her? -You didn't exactly hide her.
他该告诉你她在这干了多少事
He could've told you how much she does here.
家务，购物，每件事! 非常多
The housework, shopping, everything! That counts a lot.
我确信
I'm sure.
让我节省了很多时间. 另外...
Saves me lots of time. What's more...
...她免费做这些
...she does it for free.
所以你想要我追究这件事
So you want me to just forget it.
我今天的确睡过了头, 但我会补尝的
I did oversleep today, but I'll make up for it.
特别是在喝完咖啡后. 我来侍候你.
Especially after coffee. Let me serve it.
告诉我什么时侯
Say when.
这些破烂屋子需要再刷点漆
All these shacks need another lick of paint.
他们看起来就像垃圾箱!
They look like hell!
它们一定会更好看的
They sure would look better.
或许有个办法
There may be a way.
你和你的女朋友能做得到吗?
Can you and your girl do it?
你开玩笑? 它需要一个团队来做.
Are you kidding? It'd take a whole company.
我们会一直干到二千年
We'd still be at it in the year 2000.
当你坠入情网时, 还会考虑时间吗? 并且你俩已经组成了一个团队
When you're in love, what's time? And you two already make a company.
好的, 但你给她多少工资?
Okay, but how will you pay her?
真有趣. 你刚刚才要我忘了见到她.
Funny. You just asked me to forget I saw her.
如果我付她工资，那我不就吃亏了?
How can I make ends meet if I pay her?
依照你自己的节奏工作吧
Just do it at your own pace.
我会让你来处理 我会从老乔治那里订购油漆
I'll leave you to it. I'll order the paint from old George.
别担心，努力工作
Don't worry, just plug away.
别忘了弄湿地面
And don't forget to moisten the grounds.
那个胖笨蛋是谁
Who was that fat slob?
物主
The owner.
他想要什么
What did he want?
没有什么， 他只要我们干点刷漆工作
Nothing, he just wants us to do a little paint job.
好极了！我喜欢刷漆
Terrific. I love to paint.
五百间平房，五百前厅
500 bungalows. 500 fronts.
一千五百墙板 数以千计百页窗
1,500 sides. Thousands of shutters.
只是一点刷漆工作!
Just a little paint job!
你们俩重新刷全部的木屋?
Are you two going to repaint all these shacks?
也该重新刷那些人
Should repaint the people too.
闭嘴！乔治
Just shut your mouth, George.
-你向我发脾气吗? -你怎么猜到的?
-Hell, are you mad at me? -How did you guess?
不要在贝蒂面前讨论它. 去吹你的萨克斯管吧
Don't talk about it in front of Betty. Go play your sax.
我只是告识诉这些好人我们要给他们的屋子刷漆
I just told these nice folks we're painting their house.
我做什么?
What shall I paint?
你刷窗，我来刷剩下的
The shutters. And I'll do the rest.
-什么使你烦恼? -什么也没有.
-What's bugging you? -Nothing.
赢的人帮助其他人
The winner helps the other.
-准备! -希望她不会失败
-Ready! -I hope she doesn't fall.
她不会，她还年轻
She won't. She's young.
我赢了!
I win!
-我开始刷墙吗? -当然.
-Shall I start on the wall? -Sure.
太无聊了
What a drag.
该死!
Shit!
你真是个笨蛋!
You goofed!
有什么错误吗?
What's wrong?
是我的错. 我忘了告识诉你不要越过那个墙角
My fault. I forgot to tell you not to go past the corner.
油漆刷太大
The brush is too big.
现在看来那一面已开始
Now it looks as if that side is started.
但是谁关心?
But who cares?
谁关心?
Who cares?
你不会只刷一边吧,不是吧?
You're not going to paint just one side, are you?
你想为他们刷整间屋子?
You want to do the whole shack for them?
-是的, 当然. -当然?
-Yeah, of course. -Of course?
-你是个油漆房屋冠军. -你期望什么?
-You're a champion house painter. -What do you expect?
干吧，我来抓着桶
Go on, I'll hold the bucket.
又想睡觉吗?
Fallen asleep again?
瞌睡虫.
Sleepy warm slug.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
微笑，把油漆棍举高点
Smile! Hold the roller higher.
让我看看!
Let me see!
这样好极了!
It's terrific!
-我看起来很难看. -你为什么摆出那种表情?
-I look awful. -Why'd you pull that face?
我们厌烦刷漆了，就再刷一间
We're fed up with painting. Just one more.
停下，我们已经刷五十间了，贝蒂
Stop, we've already got 50, Betty.
我们喝啤酒吧
Let's have a beer.
那肥佬又来了
That fat slob again.
你们的确工作很辛苦
You sure are working hard.
你盼望什么?
What do you expect?
你们真是太棒了. 我们来看你们是否能保持这种速度
You're fantastic. We'll see if you can keep up the pace.
他刚才说什么?
What did he just say?
他什么也没说!
He didn't say anything!
你什么意思，“速度”?
What do you mean, "the pace"?
不要担心，亲爱的年轻女士...
Don't worry, my dear young lady...
...我没有要求你们不停地工作, 我不是一个恶魔.
...I'm not asking you to do it nonstop, I'm not a monster.
继续取凉吧. 对你们很合适.
Just keep fanning yourself. Suits you nicely.
不停地做什么?
To do what nonstop?
所有的平房
All the bungalows.
他在开玩笑,是不是?
He's kidding, right?
我像是在开玩笑吗?
Do I look like I am?
我会重新考虑
I'll think it over.
贝蒂！停下！
Betty! Stop!
-你疯了! -你不介意刷你这破木箱!
-You're insane! -I don't mind painting your crate!
让它看起来更时髦!
Makes it look more sporty!
但我不会刷你的木屋!
But I won't paint your shacks!
她疯了!
She's insane!
刷一下就焕然若新!
One wipe and it'll be like new!
她月经来了，这里的风把她吹得有点疯了
She's having her period, and this wind's enough to drive you crazy.
我确信她有歉意
I'm sure she's sorry.
我甚至愿为你刷街灯柱!
I'll even paint the lampposts for you!
电力公司会做那个，你个笨蛋!
The electricity company does that, you jerk!
你好！是我
Hi. It's me.
你跟那笨蛋说了什么?
What did you tell that asshole?
除非你工作，他不让你留在这
Look, he wouldn't let you stay unless you worked.
把所有木屋都刷了，简直就像谋杀
It's murder to paint all those shacks.
在某种程度上，是的
In a way, yes.
在某种程度上？该死，他们全是杂种!
In a way? Shit, they're all bastards!
我们该割断他们的喉咙!
We should cut all their throats!
-那能帮上什么忙? -你毫无自尊心吗?
-How would that help? -Have you no pride?
我愿把整个市镇都刷成粉红色的...
I'll paint the whole town pink...
...只要能和你呆在一起，小猫!
...just to stay with you, kitten!
你疯了! 看看那浑蛋如何对待我们!
You're nuts! Look what shit we're in with that asshole!
你让他诈骗你，为了什么? 告诉我!
You let him screw you, and for what? Tell me!
我们处境相同!
We're all in the same boat!
不要胡说八道!
Stop talking bullshit!
如果我不钦佩你，我怎么会爱你?
How can I love you if I can't admire you?
我们在这只是在学习如何死亡!
We're only learning how to die here!
看看外面的风, 吹起报纸碎片?
See the wind outside, blowing bits of newspapers by?
某天来自北方的报纸, 下一次来自南方...
Papers from the North one day, from the South the next...
...都是胡说 我们夹在中间!
...always the same bullshit, and we're in between!
现在, 听着, 我们有舒适的地方做爱...
Now, look, we've got a nice pad to screw in...
...原来你才疯了!
...so it's you who's nuts!
你这懦夫! 你们男人总是有问题! 该死!
You coward! Something's always wrong with you guys! Shit!
你是愚蠢的贱人!
And you're a stupid bitch!
男人总是有问题!
Always something wrong with a guy!
这里太黑了，又散发出臭味！
It's dark in here, your house stinks!
我烦透了，我在这不能呼吸!
I'm fed up! I can't breathe in here!
我要好好改善你房屋的状况，让我能呼吸!
I'm going to fix your house up good so I can breathe!
全是胡说!
Sort your shit out a bit!
我会给你看得!
I'll fucking show you!
-那个不行，贝蒂! -它为什么特殊?
-Not that one, Betty! -Why is it so special?
情感成份.
Sentimental attachment.
-这些都是什么? -希特勒的论文集.
-What's all this? -Hitler's memoirs.
请给我那个盒子!
Give me that box. Please!
-是你写的吗? -是的，很久以前.
-Did you write all this? -Yeah. Ages ago.
你写了这么多?
You filled all these notebooks?
-是的, 但毫无价值, 只是废物! -关于什么的?
-Yeah, but it's nothing, just crap! -About what?
我几乎忘了的东西
Just stuff I'd almost forgotten.
没人能忘记像那样的东西!
No one forgets stuff like that!
难道你现在不想上床吗?
Won't you come to bed now?
不
No.
别动它!
Leave it!
你现在不能开始读它!
You can't start reading that now!
为什么不能?
Why not?
封面上的号码表示顺序?
The numbers on the covers show the order?
是的
That's right.
贝蒂是阅读它的第一个人
Betty was the first one to have read it.
屋中终于寂静
Quiet had returned.
在三十岁，你开始明白...
At 30, you begin to know...
...生命意义，渴望获得机会.
...what life's about, and you enjoy a break.
要咖啡吗?
Want some coffee?
一块或二块糖?
One lump or two?
那么二块吧.
Two lumps, then.
好的, 我现在要出去
Right, well, I'm off.
你喜欢吗?
Do you like it?
是你！你在那做什么?
Oh, it's you. What are you doing there?
刷西斯廷教堂.
Painting the Sistine Chapel.
只有一次工作. 稍后刷屋子里面吗?
Working for once. Will you do the insides afterwards?
是的,把你的家具盖起来.
Yeah, cover up your furniture.
我现在开始 稍后你来看我女朋友.
I'll start now. Come and see my girls afterwards.
是你制造出那些吵闹声吗?
Is that you making all that racket?
我只是在打蚊子.
Just squashing a mosquito.
别鬼混了 这里没蚊子
Quit fooling around, it's too early for mosquitoes.
看 它就在墙上蠕动
Look, you can see it squirming in a puddle of blood.
看来太阳已经晒到你了
Looks like the sun has got to you.
我开始的时候感到有点累，但是现在我进入状态了
I felt tired earlier but now I'm on form.
这就是我的女孩. 她很可爱吧?
Look at my little girl. Isn't she cute?
就是她吗? 她不是童子鸡.
That's your little girl? She's no spring chicken.
你想什么呢?
What do you expect?
这是什么？我的生日？
What's this? Is it my birthday?
不是，宝贝，只是二人晚餐
No, baby, just dinner for two.
-它是什么? -淡水蚌.
-What is it? -Mussels.
坐下. 我来上菜
Sit down. I'll dish up in a while.
看起来很棒
Looks great.
我在作梦
I'm dreaming.
喝酒!
Drink!
喜欢吗?
Like it?
-我知道那个味道. -还没完呢
-I know that smell. -That's not all.
火鸡加粟子，你喜欢吗?
Turkey with chestnuts. Do you like that?
喜欢，尤其是在每年的这个时候.
Love it. Especially at this time of year.
-什么场合? -等一下，让我看看你.
-What's the occasion? -Wait, let me look at you.
我想起你写的那些.
When I think you wrote that.
我生平从未读过这类文章
I've never read anything like it.
你没有认识到.
You don't realise.
我现在知道你为何来到这个地方. 写这些东西.
Now I see why you came to this hole. To write that.
想到你刷木屋，就让我很疯狂
To think you paint shacks drives me crazy.
这世界不是为我创造的
This world wasn't exactly made for me.
我们会处理的，吻我
We'll see about that. Kiss me.
我来这本不打算写作
I hadn't come to that hole to write.
稍后我才开始写作
It was later that I started writing.
使我生气勃勃
So I could feel alive.
你们上午十一时开工 现在下午4点了
Mornings you start at 1 1 and now afternoons at 4!
这里太热了! 但我们一直做到天黑, 很多小时!
It's too hot! But I work till dark, lots of hours!
那是致死的原因!
That's the end of that!
-不要像那样跟他说话! -我不是在和你说话!
-Don't talk to him like that! -I'm not talking to you!
-知道你在跟谁说话吗? -我的雇员!
-Know who you're talking to? -An employee!
在世的最伟大的作家 ，肥佬!
The greatest writer alive, fat ass!
从他脸看不出来! 她甚至没有穿内裤!
Doesn't show on his face! And she hasn't even got panties on!
你看仔细些, 傻瓜!
Take a good look, fucker!
闭嘴！快点 看仔细些!
Shut up, you! Go on, have a stare!
-她是个泼妇! -你没有受伤吗?
-She's a real hellcat! -Not hurt, are you?
你这浑蛋！现在，赶走那女孩! 她歇斯底里的.
You asshole! Now, get rid of that girl! She's hysterical.
我不想再看到她!
I don't ever want to see her again!
她是个贱货!
She's a public menace!
你应该感到羞耻! 婊子!
You should be ashamed! Bitch!
我认为我该去工作了
I think I'll get to work.
贝蒂，我去工作 了
Hey, Betty, I'm going to work.
她真地发怒了
She's in a real frenzy.
她喜欢做家务
She loves housework.
那炖锅报销了
There goes the saucepan.
烫衣板
The ironing board.
电唱机
The record player.
我的格什温唱片
My Gershwin record.
真的
Really.
我不愿有像她那样的女管家
I wouldn't want a housekeeper like her.
-我不怪你. -我是说, 真地
-I don't blame you. -I mean, really.
她快结束了
She's almost through.
你的住所现在看起来很整洁.
Your pad will look very Zen now.
好的. 你来吗?
Okay. Are you coming?
-你疯 了! -我们走吗?
-You're insane! -Shall we go?
什么 我听不到!
What? I can't hear!
我爱你！我爱你!
I love you! I love you!
-再说一次! -我爱你！我爱你!
-Once more! -I love you! I love you!
我爱他!
I love him!
我们本可乘那火车.
We could've taken the train.
但这是个冒险
But this is an adventure.
-我们投宿在谁的房子里? -我最好的朋友的. 她是寡妇
-Whose house are we staying at? -My best friend's. She's a widow.
-如果她不在家呢? -我们去参观蒙玛特!
-What if she's not home? -We'll visit Montmartre!
不是很棒吗? 马恩河 所有的房间都能看到河的风景...
Isn't it great? The Marne. All the rooms have a river view...
...还有游船和鸭子 黄褐色!
...with the barges and the ducks. Rusty!
嘿, 水龙头漏水
Hey, the tap's leaking.
坦白说，自从弗兰克死后， 每件东西都装在罐子里
Everything's going to pot since Frank died. Honestly.
你选了13号
Hey, you've chosen number 1 3.
这不是五星级大酒店, 不要怀疑
It's no 5-star hotel, no doubt about that.
这个房间已经空了一个星期 其它的空了6个月
The room's been free a week and the rest of the place 6 months.
我住在楼下，它怎么抓你的?
I live just downstairs. Well, how does it grab you?
-我们能租下它吗？ -租它？当然能
-Can we rent it? -Rent it? Of course you can.
我宁愿有像你一样的房客
I'd rather have tenants like you.
13号，想一下，也不算太坏
Number 1 3. Just think, our luck's in.
-还有张双人床 -双人床！太棒了
-There's a double bed too. -A double bed! Great!
底部需要变一下
The base needs changing.
很高兴看到你们 我有时感到孤单
It's good to see you together. I feel lonely at times.
别担心 来吧，我们会照顾你
Don't worry. Come on, we'll look after you.
他? 那里? 和你?
Me? There? With you?
我们三个? 和你? 现在?
All three of us? With you? Now?
想要个拥抱吗?一个拥抱 当心
Want a cuddle? A little cuddle. Watch out.
哦，一个热吻 我也要 我也想要一个!
Oh, kisses. Me too. I want one too!
我们会早点弄你的头发
We'll get out of your hair soon.
你想呆多久就呆多久 我很高兴你的来访,你知道的
You can stay as long as you like. I'm glad you're around, you know.
你知道的
You know that.
告诉我, 你现在还没有意中人?
Tell me, haven't you got a man right now?
有时有, 有时没有 像其他人一样, 没什么大不了的.
Some days I do, some days I don't. Like everybody, nothing serious.
我有条狗.
I've got my dog.
等一下. 看那.
Wait. Look. There.
你得找下其他人
Fetch! You should find someone anyway.
我愿意. 但你知道男人. 在我看来, 不是那么容易
I'd love to. But you know men. With my looks, it's not that easy.
嘿, 秃头!看!
Hey, Rusty! Look!
走过我房门的人肯定感到惊奇
The one who gets through my door will have to be a real wonder.
好的,你有关系吗?
Well, have you got your bearings?
-租金如何付? -作为交换，你可干点零碎工作.
-And the rent? -You can do odd jobs in exchange.
当然，我是个水管工人
Sure. I'm a plumber.
水管工人? 好极了，我的厕所坏了
A plumber? Great. My toilet's broken.
-我会买材料 -我会从建筑工地偷点
-I'll buy the stuff. -I'll swipe it from a building site.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
除非被打出来，名著也不能阅读
Not even a masterpiece gets read unless it's typed.
-你懂打字吗? -当然
-Can you type? -Of course.
你打算把它们全打出来?
You plan to type all that?
祝你好运，甜心
Good luck, sweetie.
把那个给我
Give that to me.
-你打了多少? -第一页
-How far are you? -On page 1 .
走开，你把我搞糊涂了
Go away, you'll make me screw up.
一点凉水
A bit of cold water.
该死,水笼头漏水
Shit, the tap's leaking.
Lisa今晚又出去了
Lisa's out again tonight.
-仍和以前那样喜欢? -你不要担心
-Still like it as much? -Don't you worry.
-我的文章或许永不会出版,贝蒂. -你开玩笑?
-I may never get published, Betty. -Are you kidding?
这是个奇怪的世界, 宝贝.
It's a strange world, baby.
你现在不吃吗
Won't you eat now?
我为你煮了几个鸡蛋.
I've boiled some eggs for you.
我没时间
I don't have time.
-你为何瞪着我? -我认为你很美丽
-Why are you staring at me? -I think you're beautiful.
那么来亲我.
Then come and kiss me.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
修理水龙头，它漏水
Repairing the tap. It leaks.
-你不冷吗? -不. 我不是很暖和.
-Aren't you cold? -No. I'm not very warm.
-贝蒂仍在打字吗? -她进行得很顺利
-Betty still typing? -She's getting on okay.
你怎么样？
And you?
你的眼睛熠熠有神
Your eyes are shining.
哦, 左格. 我刚和人做爱
Oh, Zorg. I just fucked.
热烈交合
Really fucked.
没什么好笑的
Nothing to laugh about.
他是谁?
Who is he?
你会遇到他
You'll meet him.
-我去睡了 -我也去, 马上.
-I'm going to bed. -Me too, in a minute.
嗅到焦味了吗?
Smell anything burning?
没有 为何问？
No, why?
秃头, 来吧
Rusty, come on.
左格, 来看一下
Zorg, come and have a look.
猜我在打什么
Guess what I'm typing.
"T-H-E E-N-D"（结束）
"T-H-E E-N-D"
不, 真的?
No, really?
你对我全属误解
You've got me all wrong.
你是作家，不是水管工! 我打了什么？一部小说
You're a writer, not a plumber! What did I type? A novel!
不要如此愚蠢！ 如果你喜欢去赌赛马...
Don't be so dumb! Play the races if you like...
...我不在乎, 但不要做一个水管工, 好吗?
...I don't care, but stop being a plumber, okay?
看到这名单了吗? 本市所有出版商的名单!
See this list? All the publishers in this dumb town!
所有人?
All of them?
我要去买本赛马手册.
I think I'll go buy a racing mag.
它会是什么?
What'll it be?
-龙舌兰酒 -我们没有
-Tequila. -We don't have that.
那就法国绿茴香酒
Pernod, then.
三杯.
Make it a triple.
嘿，我们是在马恩河的堤岸上吗?
Hey, are we on the banks of the Marne here?
多少房间? 13?
How many rooms? 13?
坦白地说，在马恩河的堤岸上，13间房子能 挣到钱
13 rooms on the banks of the Marne can bring in cash. Honestly.
只要弯下腰来拾 那就是为什么我是驼背. 这里.
Just bend down to pick it up. That's why I'm a hunchback. Here.
-你不是驼背 -我是
-You're no hunchback. -I am.
你不是驼背, 你很英俊.
You're no hunchback, you're handsome.
快点, 喝光, 它是基安蒂红葡萄酒
Come on, drink up, it's Chianti.
有帕尔马火腿, 摩泰台拉香肚 和自制的馅饼
And there's Parma ham, mortadella and homemade pate.
士麦那橄榄 士麦那橄榄
And Smyrna olives. Smyrna olives.
-这是涡轮发动机吗？ -不, 它是UFO牌汽车
-Is this a turbo? -No, it's a UFO.
-是你的吗? -不
-Is it yours? -No.
-价钱昂贵 -非常正确
-Costs a lot! -Too right.
-装备ABS. -那是什么?
-It's got ABS. -What's that?
优秀的U+5239车系统
Great brakes.
-时速一百五十里 -我父亲有一辆
-And it can do 1 50 mph. -My dad has one.
你父亲有辆绿色老爷车!
Your dad has an old crate, and it's green!
左格来了!
There's Zorg!
-赛马手册呢? -卖完了
-And the racing mag? -Sold out.
欢乐，小鲨鱼，你先喝汤
Lovejoy, Baby Shark and Eat-Your-Soup in the lead!
真快乐
Lovejoy out.
你是左格? 埃迪 西奥勒
You're Zorg? Eddy Sayolle.
他是你的有非凡成就的人?
Is he your wonder boy?
外面是你的UFO车吗?
Is that your UFO outside?
当然，她不是很美丽吗?
You bet. Beautiful, isn't she?
外面有些人正在拆你的车.
Some kids are taking her apart.
-最好给他们车钥匙 -你开完笑.
-Better just give them the keys. -You're kidding.
我们去公路兜兜风，怎么样? 1 50!
How about a ride on the motorway? 1 50!
不, 我们得邮寄手稿
No, we have to mail the manuscripts.
她的臀部多么迷人
The ass she's got.
小心!
Be good!
我有个好主意
I've got a better idea.
龙舌兰酒快车!
Tequila rapido!
你拿一条毛巾和一个玻璃杯...
You take a towel and a glass...
... 龙舌兰酒和汽水
...and tequila and Schweppes.
说一句祈祷的话!
Say a prayer!
-有用吗? -当然.
-Will it work? -Sure.
吻一下
Kiss.
它出去了!
Off it goes!
所以你写书?
So you write books?
写作能维持生活吗？
Do you make any bread doing that?
有时侯!
Sometimes!
你有成功的把握. 坐办公桌的舒适工作
You've got it made. A soft job behind a desk.
你写作，然后获得金钱报酬!
You write, then go get the cash!
你擅长写哪一方面的书?
And what is your branch?
历史小说！
Historical novels!
快餐店是你的吗?
Is that joint yours?
是的, 比萨
Yes, Pizza Stromboli!
埃迪的比萨营业室!
Eddy's Pizza Parlour!
我忘了你写那方面的书.
I forget what kind of books you write.
科学幻想小说!
Science fiction!
该死!
Shit!
-有什么问题吗? -邮箱里除了垃圾什么也没有.
-What's wrong? -Nothing but rubbish in the post.
才4天而已.4天不算什么
It's only been four days. Four days is nothing.
我们拥抱一下
Let's have a cuddle.
是的, 我们拥抱一下. 哪里? 在这?
Yeah, let's have a cuddle. Where? Down here?
-楼上. -酒吧后面.
-Upstairs. -Behind the bar.
-楼上. -那很沉闷
-Upstairs. -It's depressing up there.
每次总是这样
It's always the same each time.
你至少要相信我
Do you at least trust me?
贝蒂,过来看!
Betty, come and see!
发生什么事?
What's going on?
我们沉湎于声色！
We're sinking into debauchery!
太棒了
Fantastic!
不要搞乱我的东西
Don't mess up my stuff.
他要搬进来 你赞同吗?
He's moving in. Are you okay with that?
让我们庆祝一下
Let's celebrate.
-不要摸! -他们也做了男性适用品吗?
-Don't touch! -Do they make them for men too?
试穿一件.
Try one on.
这是我唯一感到舒服的服装
It's the only thing I feel good in.
100%纯丝质，也有红色的
1 00% silk. There's a red one too.
感觉很性感
Feels sexy.
我们喝杯或者怎么样？
Are we going to drink or what?
星期日邮局休息
There's no mail on Sunday.
哦, 是的, 没错
Oh, yeah, that's right.
来喝杯咖啡
Come and have a coffee.
羊角面包
Croissant.
事情就是这么发展, 是吧?
That's the way things go, huh?
-我有工作给你们俩干 -什么样的工作?
-I've got a job for you two. -Like what?
什么样的工作? 就是一个工作.
Like what? A job.
我的米兰爱犬去了那里?
Where's my Milanese?
别忘了阳台上面的开胃酒!
Don't forget those aperitifs on the terrace!
快点, 亲爱的!
Hurry up, honey!
你买到三号了吗?
Did you get number 3?
-这是你的 -总是像这样吗?
-This is yours. -Is it always like this?
-九号? -九号在哪里?
-And 9? -Where is 9?
通常在八号和十号之间，晚安
Between 8 and 1 0 usually. Good night!
那些酒!
Those drinks!
一切顺利吗?
Doing okay?
-你买到九号了吗? -九号在哪里?
-Did you get 9? -Where is 9?
这胖女士
The fat lady.
我们可否点菜？真的
May we order? Really!
厕所在那里?
Where are the toilets?
给我一杯那不勒斯, 不要凤尾鱼
Give me a Neapolitan, no anchovies.
不, 等等 我不知道选什么
No, hold on. I don't know what to choose.
选最贵的. 它一定是最好的.
Have the most expensive one. It must be the best.
一份法式馅饼. 我要一份法式馅饼
A Margherita. I'll have a Margherita.
法式馅饼里有凤尾鱼吗?
Are there anchovies in the Margherita?
-对不起 -不! 没有凤尾鱼!
-Sorry? -No! There are no anchovies!
那么一份带凤尾鱼的法式馅饼 我还能点火腿吗?
A Margherita with anchovies then. Can I have ham too?
里面有火腿
There's ham in it.
哪里有?
Where does it say that?
没有标出来
It's not written in the stars.
坦白地说, 字体真的比较小.
Honestly, it's really small print.
-给我一些玻璃杯. -对不起?
-Get yourself some glasses. -Excuse me?
她完全疯了! 她快把我的脑袋撕成两半了.
She's totally crazy! She almost tore my head off.
冷静. 你考虑过我的邀请了吗, Marie?
Calm down. Have you considered my offer yet, Marie?
来吧, 微笑.
Come on, smile.
我忍受够了
I've had it.
坐在五号桌的贱人 我迟早要好好打她一顿
That bitch at number 5. I'll hit her pretty soon.
我会应付她
I'll handle her.
有什么问题吗?
Is there some problem?
那女孩是不是呆子还是怎么的?
Is that girl an idiot or what?
我说要带凤尾鱼的比萨，不要火腿!
I said pizza with anchovies, not ham!
上面加些辣椒汁
Try some pimento sauce on it.
不. 现在, 给我上我点的食物.
No. Now, give me what I ordered.
我明白我能做什么
I'll see what I can do.
我点的食物很棒，没有问题
Mine is great. No problem.
你需要什么?
What do you need?
你知到新式烹调吗?
Do you know nouvelle cuisine?
全是垃圾
That's just crap.
等会你会看到"反胃烹饪" 小心
Wait till you see my "repel cuisine." Watch.
你点了能找到的最垃圾的食物...
You pick out the worst garbage you can find...
...发臭的垃圾, 有汗臭的香肠...
...stinky junk, bits of sweaty sausage...
...少许蕃茄, 很好, 新鲜意大利式细面条...
...a little tomato, nice, fresh spaghetti...
...陈旧乳酪圈, 一半新鲜和一半腐烂的生菜...
...an old cheese rind, lettuce that's good and rotten...
...一枚橄榄...
...one olive...
...就制成了!
...and there you are!
现在加点阳光.
Now add a little sunshine.
我忘了最好的部分.
I forgot the best part.
-哦,该死. -你说对了.
-Oh, shit. -You said it.
你的比萨怎么样?
How's your pizza?
-热辣. -你才热辣.
-Hot. -You're the hot one.
你让我很兴奋
You're turning me on.
-小心你的衬衫. -不要紧.
-Look out for your blouse. -Doesn't matter.
-有什么问题? -我很累
-What's wrong? -I'm tired.
我没事，只是乏力
I'm okay, just tired.
再会，谢谢你
Goodbye and thank you.
多美好的夜晚
What a night.
-你写哪类书? -侦探小说
-What kind of books do you write? -Detective novels.
-有答案吗? -还没有.
-Any answer yet? -Not yet.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
-你疯了！给经理打电话！ -有什么问题?
-You're insane! Call the manager! -What's wrong?
整个晚上服务糟极 了!
The service was rotten all evening!
现在这小蠢人不愿为我拿大衣!
And now this little fool won't get my coat!
-我会付他们账单. -回去端盘子
-I'll pay their bill. -Go back to your dishes!
你疯了!
You're crazy!
你应该把她锁起来!
You should have her locked up!
把他们赶出去, 埃迪!
Throw them out, Eddy!
冷静点! 够了!
Calm down! Enough!
出什么事了?
What's the matter?
没什么, 她会没事的.
Nothing, she'll be okay.
-该死, 告诉我发生什么事了! -让我和她单独在一起
-Shit, tell me what happened! -Leave me alone with her.
往她脸上洒些水
Put water on her face.
-我去取水 -离开, 埃迪! 该死!
-I'll get some. -Beat it, Eddy! Shit!
我现在在这, 亲爱的.
I'm here now, sweetheart.
现在都结束了
It's over now.
她在睡觉吗?
Is she sleeping?
她当然在睡觉
Of course she's sleeping.
怎么了? 她患病了吗?
What was it? Is she sick?
你从不发怒吗?
Look, don't you ever get mad?
发怒, 不错，但发怒使我害怕
Mad, yes, but that scared me.
-别在意 -别说不要紧
-It's nothing. -Don't say it was nothing.
她几乎杀了那个女人
She almost killed that woman.
胡说
Bullshit.
关于你的版税....
With your royalties....
该死，不要用我的书烦扰我!
Shit, stop bugging me about my books!
我一生只写了一部书.
I've only written one in all my life.
我怀疑能否再写一部 至于版税....
And I doubt I could write another one. As for royalties....
-我认为-- -我认为什么？
-I thought-- -You thought what?
她是如此告识你的吗?
She told you that?
她发现一部手稿，以为我是天才
She found a manuscript and thinks I'm a genius.
一直等待出版商的答复
Keeps waiting for publishers to reply.
那快让她疯了
That drives her nuts.
她或许正确
She may be right.
关于什么?
About what?
你是天才
That you're a genius.
当然，读下这个,宝贝儿
You bet. Read this, toots.
联合出版社
United Books.
"很遗憾, 不. 有趣, 但是你的风格无法忍受
"Sorry, no. Amusing, but your style is unbearable.
你故意写一本内容无价值的书."
You deliberately wrote a non-book."
这奇怪的人是谁?
Who is this queer?
快藏起那个
Hide that, quick.
你今天怎样?
How are you, boys?
-他有什么问题? -有些事他十分不服气
-What's wrong with him? -Something he can't swallow.
我明白了. 好的,我感觉很好
I see. Well, I feel great.
-有信件吗? -我没有去看
-Any mail yet? -I didn't look.
贝蒂就像被切断腿筋的野马...
Betty was a wild horse that had cut her hamstrings...
...跳过一堵墙，挣扎地起来.
...jumping over a wall and was trying to get up.
她认为是草原的地方...
What she thought was a meadow...
...实际上是家畜栏.
...was a gloomy pen.
她不能忍受静止不动
She couldn't bear immobility.
她不适合那个
She was not made for that.
"我已经读了很多书, 但没有一部像这个手稿...
"I've read a lot of books, but nothing quite like the manuscript...
...你把最没有趣味的寄给我们.
...you had the poor taste to send us.
你的著作充满爱滋病迹象.
Your writing shows all the signs of AlDS.
我把你称为小说却是令人厌恶的花卉退还给你
I return this nauseating flower you call a novel.
相信我出版的判断力
Rely on me for publicity.
把它退还给它的原地...
Leave that thing where it belongs...
...在你大脑里的沼泽.
...in the quagmire of your brain.
你真诚的, 托马斯 柯拉斯."
Sincerely yours, Thomas Colas."
那只是游戏一部分
That's just part of the game.
我们一定会撞见弱智
We're bound to run into morons.
它不会毁掉我们
It won't kill us.
它不重要，亲爱的
It's not important, my love.
好吧，不要紧
Okay, it's not important.
-我要去看医生 -有什么问题?
-I'm going to a doctor. -Anything wrong?
不，只是检查我的lUD是不是没有毛病. 和我一起去?
No, just to see if my lUD is okay. Coming with me?
我先化化妆
I'll put some makeup on first.
我喜欢翻阅旧杂志, 可消除疑虑.
I love to look at old magazines, it's reassuring.
我看来很傻，给我夹克
I look silly, give me my jacket.
我穿了它很漂亮
But I look good in it.
是这个吗？没有标志
Is this it? There's no plaque.
停下，他不是聋子!
Stop it, he's not deaf!
-是吗? 我能为你做什么? -我不知道, 我的妻子--
-Yes? What can I do for you? -I don't know, my wife--
-这个是你写的吗? -那个?
-Did you write this? -That?
你能认识这个，不是吗? 谁签署的这个?
You recognise this, don't you? Who signed this?
该死的出版商!
Shitty asshole publisher!
是的，我非常愤怒!
Yes, I'm mad as hell!
-我会收拾一切. -别动它, 你这笨蛋!
-I'll clean it all up. -Leave it, you fucker!
告诉他你的意见!
Tell him what you think!
我不会谴责他的信!
I don't give a damn about his letter!
在你的写作和说话中...
In your writing as well as your speech...
...你没有展现出好品味!
...you show no notion of good taste!
你认为自己有品味？
And you think you do?
-滚出去！这是我的家! -不要碰我!
-Get out! This is my home! -Don't touch me!
你疯了!
You're crazy!
非常奇怪.
Very queer.
快点, 贝蒂. 快点.
Quick, Betty. Hurry up.
你真的疯了!
You're totally nuts!
-你为什么总是屈服? -别理像他一样的傻瓜.
-Why do you always give in? -Forget assholes like him.
-天哪, 没有东西碰到你吧. -那不是真的
-Jesus, nothing ever touches you. -That's not true.
好的, 给我证明一下!
Well, prove it!
贵族有世界上最好的橄榄.
Pharistopoli has the world's best olives.
在市场上你能找到的最好的.
The best you'll find anywhere on the market.
-不, 谢谢你,我不喝. -只是仙人掌汁.
-No, thank you, I don't drink. -It's only cactus juice.
只是因为你. 我的妻子不喜欢我喝.
Just for you. My wife doesn't like me drinking.
那是从哪来的?
Where's that from?
皱褶橄榄是最好的
Wrinkled olives are the best.
有两种:
There are two kinds:
大个的皱褶橄榄是叙利亚橄榄
The big wrinkled one is a Syrian olive.
适于做比萨
Good for pizzas.
不, 对比萨, 你最好别用那种.
No, for pizzas, you're better off with that one.
它塞满了胡椒粉, 所以它可能不是最好的选择
It's stuffed with pepper, so maybe it's not the best choice.
绿色的品种是去核的 很有趣
The green one is pitted. That's interesting.
我对去核的品种没有兴趣， 对那种有兴趣.
Pitted ones don't interest me. That one does.
-那种是为你做的, 埃迪. -试试开罗玫瑰
-That one's for you, Eddy. -Try the Rose of Cairo.
多出来的一个是为了贵族先生
One more for Mr. Pharistopholi.
Pharistopoli, 不是Pharistopholi. Pharistopoli.
Pharistopoli, not Pharistopholi. Pharistopoli.
给你. 干杯！
Here you go. Bottoms up.
来吧!
Come on!
不坏. 提供橄榄很好
Not bad. Goes well served with olives.
-多少钱? -通常地, 每公斤350元.
-How much? -Normally, they're 350 a kilo.
-什么? 每公斤350元? -是的, 公平价格.
-What? 350 a kilo? -Yes, it's a fair price.
尝一个, 左格. 再来一个龙舌兰酒快车.
Take one, Zorg. Another tequila rapido.
不, 真的, 我没有喝.
No, really, I don't drink.
对不起. 在这你点了六个品种.
Excuse me. You have the six varieties here.
8个品种分成两半, 乘以2是1 6.
Eight varieties in two halves, times two makes 1 6.
2乘以8, 1 6.
Two times eight, 1 6.
这16份都是每公斤350元?.
Each of the 1 6 varieties for 350 a kilo.
坦白地说.
Honestly.
我会拿那个.
I'll have that one.
你算的正好
You spat on my nose.
我现在想试试紫色玫瑰
I'll try the Purple Rose now.
黑色的. 黑色的是最好的.
The black one. The black one's the best.
你还没有试过这种,龙舌兰酒. 不, 不是它
You haven't tried this one, the tequila. No, that's not it.
我在说什么? 我既不起它是什么.
What am I talking about? I can't remember what it is.
-是橄榄. -我知道, 我是一个橄榄推销员.
-It's an olive. -I know, I'm an olive salesman.
它怎么样, 左格? 我们拿. 我们把它们都拿走.
How about it, Zorg? Let's take it. Let's take them all.
-你付不起. -我会付账.
-You can't have the case. -I'll pay for it.
你为那个橄榄销售员上演了一个真正的演出.
You put on a real show for that olive seller.
住手! 它是崭新的. 那些东西弄脏了皮革!
Cut it out! It's brand-new. Those things stain leather!
该死, 住手!
Shit, cut it out!
很好, 就在视线内. 该死!
Great, right in the eye. Shit!
放松, 埃迪.
Take it easy, Eddy.
给你, 先生. 看看我的车轮.
There you go, sir. Just look at my wheels.
不要浪费时间. 她有什么毛病?
Quit messing around. What's wrong with her?
我能解释.
I can explain everything.
这真的不是她的错. 事实上是我的错.
It's not really her fault. It's mine, in fact.
在某种程度上--
In a way--
不要烦恼. 我之前都已经听说了.
Don't bother. I've heard it all before.
我记下费用 然后告诉你的朋友.
I noted down the charges and spoke to your friend.
非常漂亮的女孩, 但有点紧张.
Quite a pretty girl, but a bit uptight.
他不总是那样. 我怎样放这个?
She's not always like that. How can I put this?
她有痉挛症,每个月. 男人很难理解.
She has fits, every month. It's hard for men to understand.
不要说的太远.
Don't push it too far.
不, 当然不.
No, of course not.
因此你写小说,是吗?
So you write novels, do you?
是的, 我试图出版. 它不容易.
Yes, or rather I'm trying to get published. It's not easy.
出版公司里的人都是混蛋.
They're all fucking assholes in those publishing houses.
我该知道
I should know.
呆在那, 我想给你看样东西.
Stay there, I want to show you something.
你认为这是什么?
What do you think this is?
手稿
A manuscript.
完全对
Exactly!
我开始喜欢你了
I'm getting to like you.
不论你信不信我 这些书已被拒27次了.
You won't believe me but I've had 2 7 refusals on this.
27! 他们是顶级笨蛋.
Twenty-seven! They're first-class assholes.
被拒27次  非常多
Twenty-seven refusals. That's quite a lot.
当我想起我花费在这本书上的那些年.
When I think of all the years that I've put into that book.
最好的情况, 最顽强的一个人在坚持.
All the best cases, the toughest ones are in there.
真得太令人震撼了.
It's real dynamite.
相信我, 它伤了我的感情. 非常深. 相信我.
Believe me, it hurts. It hurts a lot. Trust me.
我相信你
I trust you.
有那么多的笨蛋 他们的劣等论文集卖了上百万.
There are some dumb cops whose shitty memoirs sell millions.
那么为什么所有的出版商都针对我?
So why are the publishers all against me?
什么没法理解他们.
Don't even try to understand them.
出版商都是混蛋.
Publishers are all fucking assholes.
-感觉就像一杯酒,老兄? -当然.
-Feel like a drink, man? -You bet I do.
为了将来的成功! 不要让他们令你沮丧!
To future success! Don't let them get you down!
当我想到那些混蛋在五分钟内毁了一个人 一年的工作
When I think of those assholes ruining a year's work in five minutes.
我不能说你的朋友是对的...
I can't say your friend's right...
...但是她也没有错.
...but she's not wrong, either.
一个充满了性的警察故事素材!
A good cop story full of sex!
那是最好的一类.
That's the best kind.
党那个混蛋打电话来, 我想一下, "他会付剩下的钱."
When that asshole called, I thought, "He'll pay for the rest."
我很高兴. 我喝了一杯酒来庆祝.
I was glad. I had a drink to celebrate.
她只是抓伤了他. 他会小题大作
She only scratched him. He's making a mountain of a molehill.
8针. 我应该踢他的脑袋
Eight stitches. I'd have kicked his head in.
他们认为他们是谁? 临走前的最后一杯酒?
Who do they think they are? Fancy one for the road?
你的书就在这，非常好.
Your book's sitting here nice and warm.
像一架飞机准备起飞.
Like a plane ready to take off.
相信我, 它会出版的.
Believe you me, it'll be published.
-我不这么认为. -它会的, 我确信.
-I don't think so. -It will, I'm sure.
贝蒂怎么样? 我们能结束整件事吗?
What about Betty? Can we drop the whole thing?
该死. 我能离开这个破旧的办公室.
Shit. I could leave this shitty office.
我能去接她吗?
Can I go and get her?
该死  你不明白
Shit, you just don't understand.
你难道没看见他对那个家伙所做的事吗?
Can't you see she did all this for guys like you and me?
我知道, 但是有指控.
I know, but there's the fucking charges.
来吧, 你是警察. 一定有摆脱困境的办法.
Come on, you're a policeman. There must be some way out of it.
不容易. 有记录.
It's not easy. There are records.
好的, 我明白了.
Okay, I get it.
不, 等一下.
No, hold on.
可能有个办法
There may be a way.
那么说下去, 忏悔.
Go on then, confess.
那个家伙将不得不决定不提出起诉.
The guy would have to decide not to press charges.
那么简单
It's that simple.
-它是谁? -它是为了书展的.
-Who is it? -It's for The Book Show.
正确!
Right!
来杯酒, 甜馅饼? 你有点苍白.
Fancy a drink, sweetie-pie? You're a bit pale.
马提尼酒.
Martini.
这里.
Here.
你在那拥有的很好的位置.
Nice place you've got here.
我不是疯狂于书 不是你的错.
I'm not mad about the book. It's not your fault.
我不是特别地为你而写.
I didn't particularly write it for you.
所以我们会冰释前嫌 它是一个大误会.
So we'll just leave it there. It's one big misunderstanding.
那个女孩使我一生中唯一珍惜的东西.
That girl is the only good thing in my life.
除她之外, 什么都无关紧要
Apart from her, there's nothing.
所以你不会提起指控.
So you're not going to press charges.
记牢一件事: 我没有什么可失去的, 没有
Remember just one thing: I've nothing to lose, nothing.
快点.
Go on.
你拨错号码了. 它是电话报时服务.
You got the wrong number. It's the speaking clock.
那里. 喝光, 孩子. 喝光
There. Drink up, kiddies. Drink up.
给我你的杯子. 喝光.
Give me your glass. Drink up.
-为了什么而祝酒? -星期五!
-What's the toast to? -Friday!
生活真是太棒了!
Life is fucking great!
我不知道为什么, 但是我今晚感觉很棒.
I don't know why, but I feel great tonight.
是家人. 坦白说, 是家人
It's family. Honestly, it's family.
你可以嘲笑, 但它真的是内心的感觉.
You can laugh, but it's a real gut feeling.
只要能看见你坐在这就能温暖我的心.
Just looking at you here warms my heart.
听着, 我的内心很温暖
Look, my quiff's a mess, my heart's so warm.
给你来个吻
Big kisses to you all.
这是给你的吻
Here's a kiss for you.
你也有, 爱人.
And you too, sweetheart.
吻你的英雄, 他应得的
Kiss your hero, he deserves it.
暂停! 暂停!
Break! Break!
我有个主意
I've an idea.
来这,我孤零零地!
Come here, I'm all alone!
我就来, 宝贝!
I'm coming, baby!
它是镝！它是钠! 它是微粒！它是炸药！
It's dy! It's na! It's mite! It's dynamite!
多棒的舞女!
What a dancer!
酱汁!
The sauce!
我本愿做一个摇滚歌手！
I would've loved to be a rocker!
该死,他真地是是个摇滚歌手!
Shit, he's a real rocker!
快来帮帮我!
Come and help me!
我不用低价酒调制, 但是用香槟!
I'm not making it with cheap wine, but with champagne!
斯特龙博利比萨!
Pizza Stromboli!
有什么问题,  埃迪?
What's wrong, Eddy?
我母亲要死了
My mother's dead.
My mother's dead!
我很难过!
I feel awful!
这是你唯一的黑领带吗?
Is this your only black tie?
我必须到场
I have to be there.
她明天下葬
She's being buried tomorrow.
你现在应该休息片刻  亲爱的
You should get a little rest now, darling.
-我得换衣服 -你看起来很好
-I have to change. -You're fine.
给我我的夹克
Give me my jacket.
不 你先小睡片刻，稍后我替你叫计程车
No, sleep, and I'll call you a cab later.
560里，如果我现在启程 我会及时到达
560 miles. If I leave now, I'll make it.
你疯了  你不会单独完成 我们不会让你单独去.
You're nuts, you'll never make it in one piece. We won't let you go alone.
你有所不知，我母亲要死了
You don't realise. My mother's dead.
帮帮他
Help him.
它不好笑. 住手 它不好笑
It's not funny. Cut it out, it's not funny.
等一下,它就在那
Hold on, it's just there.
它在那. 看到那边的商店了吗?
There it is. See the shop over there?
那里. 开车穿过广场.
There. Drive across the square.
来吧!
Come on!
就是它
This is it.
-你...? -不, 她卖钢琴
-Are you...? -No, she sold pianos.
-卖了很多吗? -那不是很好
-Did she sell a lot? -That's not nice.
好的, 我们要进去吗?
Well, are we going in?
是的
It's all right.
那此喧闹声是什么？这不是基督行为
What's all this noise? It's not Christian!
-算了, 伯父. -你可怜的母亲在楼上
-Forget it, Uncle. -Your poor mother's upstairs!
足够多的耶稣基督行为 他们是我朋友
It's Christian enough. They're my friends.
我不知到你会弹
I didn't know you could play.
我不会，只懂一点
I can't. Just two or three things.
你是个奇怪有趣的女孩
You're a funny girl.
我等待找到生命意义已很久了
I waited ages for a meaning in life.
你是我遇到的最好的事
You're the best thing that ever happened to me.
你只是因为疲倦才这样说
You're only saying that because you're tired.
如果我写了那本书 我生命便有意义
If I'd written that book, I'd have a meaning in life.
它只会给我们带来麻烦.
It's only bringing us trouble.
不是因们你写了它 你是个作家
It's not because you wrote it. You are a writer.
那么我为何不能再继续创作?
Then why can't I write any more now?
因们你是个笨蛋
Because you're a damn fool.
那很好
That's nice.
你似乎很疲乏
You look tired.
我没事
I'm okay.
你看到那些星星了吗?
You see all those stars?
-有什么问题？ -没事, 我很好
-What's wrong? -Nothing, I'm fine.
你很兴奋
You're feverish.
-你在哪里? 别动. -我在这  有什么问题?
-Where are you? Stay. -I'm here. What's wrong?
我不想离开你 要支香烟吗?
I won't leave you. Do you want a cigarette?
不, 每件事都很好, 只是很好
No, everything's fine, just fine.
你看到那边的星星了吗?
Have you seen all those stars out there?
因为这个夜晚很明亮
It's because it's a clear night.
-递给我诺克曼. -什么?
-Pass me the Nuoc Man. -The what?
酱汁, 诺克曼 N-U-O-C M-A-N.
The sauce, Nuoc Man. N-U-O-C M-A-N.
一点也没有
None left.
至少是个好天气
At least it was a nice day.
有时, 我希望我是条狗
Sometimes, I wish I were a dog.
生命没有大意义
A life isn't much.
只是四张照片
Just four photos.
-喜欢这地方吗? -它全不相同
-Like it here? -It's different.
我想向你和贝蒂提出个邀请
I want to make you and Betty an offer.
留在这里管理钢琴店铺
Stay here and run the piano store.
看到了吗? 我能通灵!
See? I'm psychic!
我去问贝蒂好吗?
Shall I go ask Betty?
告诉我,你喜欢这主意吗?
Tell me, do you like the idea?
是的 我喜欢
Yes, I do.
太棒了！
Fantastic!
只是有一件事
Just one thing.
不时带些花到她坟墓
Take her flowers now and then.
-谁？ -我母亲
-Who? -My mother.
他的确赠给我们很好的礼物
He sure gave us a nice present.
不，我办不到 我不能睡在已死女人的床上
No, I just can't do it. I can't sleep in a dead woman's bed.
我知道它不好玩 不要去想它便是
I know it's no fun, but just don't think about it.
不，我不想这么做
No, I don't want to.
该死!
Shit!
我不能相信
I don't believe it.
你知时间已多么晚了吗？
Do you know how late it is?
我们可睡这折叠床
We'll just use this foldaway.
让我来做  它是力气活 呆在那
Let me, it's a mechanical thing. Stay there.
愚蠢的东西！
Stupid thing!
你想做它!
You wanted to do it!
这是什么?
What is this?
你不能做，老兄?
Can't you do it, man?
一堆垃圾
Pile of crap.
冷静些，用踏板
Calm down. Use the pedal!
踏板被卡住了, 贝蒂.
The pedal is stuck, Betty.
那么我去取工具
I'll go get the tools, then.
该死, 不要在夜晚的这个时候
Shit, not at this time of night.
我并非有意干的
I didn't do it on purpose.
停下！只会搞得更糟
Let's stop, it'll only get worse.
更安全
It's safer.
睡觉吧
Sleep away the foldaway way.
你搞什么鬼?
What are you up to?
它发出振动声 你当然不会感觉到
It gives off bad vibes. You don't feel them, of course.
现在振动已经消失了
The bad vibes are gone now!
我喜欢那地方
I liked that place.
我确定会是个好天气
I was sure it'd be a fine day.
如果他们把引擎全部开动
And it was, if they'd all had their motors tuned.
我希望没有打扰到你
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
垃圾箱旁边的是你的床垫吗?
Is that your mattress near the bins?
是的.有什么问题?
Yes. What's wrong?
好的, 我们没有处理过像那样的东西
Well, we don't handle stuff like that.
我们不想让它发生任何事
We want nothing to do with it.
我能做什么? 切碎它每天早晨吃一片?
What can I do? Cut it up and eat a piece every morning?
-我不知道. 它是你的床垫 -是的, 它是, 在某种程度上
-I don't know. It's your mattress. -Yes, it is, in a way.
他激怒你了吗? 好的，是吗?
Is he pissing you off? Well, is he?
这该死的床垫是他的吗?
Is the fucking mattress his?
-因为可怜的理由, 博比. -混蛋!
-For pity's sake, Bobby. -Bastard!
不要失去自制力.
Don't get carried away.
废物! 废物!
Filth! Filth!
混蛋! 混蛋!
Bastard! Bastard!
有一天他像那样把一个床垫扔到卡车上
One day he threw one like that in the back of the truck.
机器切断了他的手
It took his hand off.
现在, 他忍受不了床垫
Now, he can't stand mattresses.
好吧, 博比. 我们该去了.
All right, Bobby. It's time we were going.
他会没事吧?
Will he be okay?
你抽烟了吗?
Have you got a smoke?
一根烟? 当然
A smoke? Sure.
-它们是同性恋香烟. -当然.
-They're homo cigarettes. -Sure.
再见.
See you.
该死, 你一直工作很努力
Shit, you've been working hard.
-我打扫了整个屋子. -看起来很棒.
-I've cleaned the whole house. -It's looking great.
老人已经死了 你要干什么?
The old woman died a second time. What were you up to?
到镇上观光
Looking around town.
这可是个非常大的地方 我想我们得找辆车
It's a pretty big place. I guess we'll need a car.
当然，我们也需要钱
Sure, we'll need money too.
-给你的礼物 -黄油?
-Present for you. -Buttered?
当然 那也值钱
Of course. And that costs money too.
早餐时间. 酒吧开门了
Breakfast time. The bar's open.
隔壁的养乳牛者是个白化病者并且有一头红发
The dairyman next door is an albino and a redhead.
红发的白化病者穿着白色的外套...
A redhead albino in a white coat...
...每只手都拿着一瓶牛奶 你能想象吗?
...with a bottle of milk in each hand. Can you imagine that?
它会让我感到毛骨悚然
It would give me the creeps.
它会让你感到毛骨悚然 那就是我的感觉
It would give you the creeps. That's exactly how I felt.
递一下糖
Pass the sugar.
白化病者. 奇怪的人.
Albino. Weirdo.
我们应该在这附近找点工作
We should do some work around here. It's not exactly modern.
天哪!  有些人太大胆了! 过来看
Jesus, some people have got a nerve! Come and see.
快点! 看那个!
Hurry up! Look at that!
-有什么问题? -人行道上的轿车
-What's wrong? -The car on the sidewalk.
他鼓起勇气
He's got some nerve.
你是说他是个混蛋 我会证明给他看
You mean he's a fucking bastard. I'll show him.
什么勇气. 黄色的
What nerve. A yellow one too.
真漂亮 看看这光滑的车壳
It's a real beauty. Look at the finish on it.
我肯定留下了钥匙
I bet the shithead left the keys.
-你疯了? -我们去兜风
-Have you gone mad? -Let's go for a drive.
-不  你疯了 -贝蒂 下来
-No, you're crazy. -Come down, Betty.
快点
Come on.
-你在干什么? -快点，上来
-What are you doing? -Come on, get in.
你疯了
You're nuts.
看看: 皮革座椅,桃花心木 仪表板, 晶体管收音机
Look at this: leather seats, mahogany dashboard, transistor radio.
-听到那嗡嗡声了吗? -当然. 听着, 你真地疯了.
-Hear that hum? -Sure. Look, you're totally nuts.
不要担心. 他肯定是同性恋才有这样的车
Don't worry. He has to be a homo to have a car like this.
他可能是同性恋，但是你疯了
He may be a homo, but you're nuts.
冷静点
Calm down.
停下
Stop here.
就在这
Right here.
-等一下 -这里，现在
-Hold on. -Here. Now.
我们已开到路的尽头, 无论如何
We've run out of road, in any case.
开到那里
Drive up there.
我们到这来看风景，不是吗? 太棒了
We're up here for the view, are we? It's great.
你疯了. 你想什么?
You're crazy. What's got into you?
在一辆像这样的车上 你可能会变成同性恋
In a car like this, you might have turned homo.
用完一箱汽油
Guys freak out over a full tank of gas.
大型汽车是我们文明的最后曙光
Big cars are the last flash of our civilisation.
我们身无一文
I thought we were broke.
我们现在确身无分文
We are now.
我把文明的最后曙光放在你的脚边
I lay the last flash of a civilisation at your feet.
你疯了
You're crazy.
-你们俩没事吧? -很好
-Are you two okay? -Fine.
我们一直在清理家具
We've been cleaning and shifting furniture.
太棒了
That's great.
这些地板有点阴暗
These naked floorboards are a bit gloomy.
-蓝色怎么样? -为什么?
-How about blue? -Why?
我认为蓝色很好, 暖颜色.
I think blue's a nice, calm colour.
好的, 给它们刷蓝颜色
All right, paint them blue.
我烦你已很久了
I've bored you long enough now.
你不烦我
You're not boring me.
等一下, 贝蒂 想要--
Wait, Betty wants--
我几乎忘了.
I almost forgot.
贝蒂要拆毁那两堵墙
Betty wants to knock out two walls.
埃迪? 你能听到我吗?
Eddy? Can you hear me?
没事, 只是两堵小墙
It's nothing, just two thin little walls.
你什么意思, "没事"? 你们俩都疯了.
What do you mean, "nothing"? You're both nuts.
等一下, 想象那堵墙...
Wait, imagine that wall...
...是我们和阳光普照的草原间的障碍物
...as a barrier between us and a sunny meadow.
我们受小小屏障所烦扰不是对我们 的侮辱吗?
Isn't it an insult to let a silly little barrier bug us?
好的, 但是要从容不迫，现在
Okay, but go easy, now.
不用担心 我们没有疯
Don't worry, we're not crazy.
好的，再见!
All right, bye!
我看起来像洛基电影中的史泰龙吗?
Do I look like Stallone in Rocky IV, baby?
不 像是你在写的你的书
No, like you're writing your book.
我不明白拆毁和写书有何关系
I don't see what demolition has to do with writing.
我不惊讶.
I'm not surprised.
想和我一起去购物吗?
Want to go shopping with me?
你想去吗?
Do you want to?
好的,我会去, 那么.
Okay, I'll go, then.
你在那干什么？
What are you doing there?
我正在晒我的臀部
I'm warming my ass.
我给你买了爆米花
I bought you some popcorn.
给我钥匙，我来开车
Give me the keys. I'll drive.
该死的变速箱!
Fucking gearbox!
当然, 它是变速箱
Sure, it's the gearbox.
再努力一点, 我们将创造一项当地的事故纪录
Try a bit harder, we'll set a new local accident record.
我不会再进那辆破汽车.
I won't get in that shitty crate again.
你今天糟透了!
You're acting like shit today!
你精神不正常!
You're out of your mind!
冷静点！让我看看
Calm down! Let me see.
停下!
Stop!
该死  贝蒂，停下
Shit, Betty, stop!
你真的激怒了我!
You're really pissing me off!
够了!
Enough!
贝蒂, 求你了!
Betty, please!
结束了,好吗?
It's over, okay?
-怎么回事? -没事
-What's going on here? -Nothing.
她感觉不好,所以我打了她
She didn't feel well, so I slapped her.
我恐怕她会大发脾气
I was afraid she'd have a fit.
-我知道这很难理解. -为何说难理解?
-I know that's hard to believe. -Why is that hard to believe?
我们只是在慢跑
We'd just been jogging.
-慢跑有帮助吗? -许多，是的.
-Does jogging help? -A lot, yeah.
那个年轻女士现在怎么样?
And how is the little lady now?
理查德, 我跟你说别拿枪指着我
Richard, I told you not to point that at me!
我瞄准的是他，不是你
I'm aiming at him, not you!
把那东西放下!
Put that thing down!
看看他的鞋
Look at his shoes.
某天我们也看到过一个绿发的家伙
We saw a guy with green hair one day too.
世界就像这样. 不应停留在细节上
The world's like that. Don't go by details.
-只是意外 -你看到了?
-It's only an accident. -You see?
如果我们某天把事情弄砸了 那就是你的错
If we screw up one day, it'll be your fault.
你抓伤了他? 不 你想是带着一把枪!
Did you search him? No. You just like to carry a pistol!
不要疯了. 看看他们
Don't get mad. Look at them.
我在他动之前会打爆他的头
I'd smack his head before he could move.
你有四十年经验
I've had 40 years' experience.
那么自己做, 我退出.
Then work it out alone, count me out.
你什么态度!
You've got a fucking attitude!
开始! 住手! 我给你两秒钟!
Open up! Cut it out! I'll give you two seconds!
好的, 我会停!
Okay, I'll stop!
下次,我会开枪!
Next time, I'll shoot!
我们的新兵有良好的训练...
Our recruits get good training...
...但是这打击了他们的勇气!
...but it wrecks their nerves!
对不起, 是我的错.
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
你们是过路的吗?
Are you just passing through?
不, 我们经营钢琴商店.
No, we run the piano store.
你是埃迪的朋友?
You're friends of Eddy's?
你应该早说! 我们一起回去.
You should've said so! We'll drive you back.
来吧, 贝蒂.
Come on, Betty.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
-今天卖了一架钢琴? -当然, 尽量笑吧
-Selling a piano today? -Sure, laugh all you like.
-哦, 混蛋! -对不起.
-Oh, fuck! -Sorry.
你等一下.
Just you wait.
-鲍勃, 有时间吗? -当然.
-Bob, got a minute? -Sure.
你通常用来写在窗户上的东西, 我能拿一些吗?
That stuff you use to write on the window, can I have some?
-白粉. -是的, 白粉.
-Whitening. -Yeah, whitening.
好的, 你怎么看? 不坏, 是吧?
Well, what do you think? Not bad, huh?
"成本价格的钢琴, 一生仅有一次的的廉价出售."
"Pianos at cost price, once-in-a-lifetime sale."
商业第一法则: 让自己引人注意
Rule number one in business: Get yourself noticed.
第二法则: 廉价销售
Rule number 2: Have a great sales pitch.
一生仅有一次的的廉价出售!
Once-in-a-lifetime sale!
好的. 我去清洗 然后准备午餐.
Right. I'll go and wash, then get lunch ready.
它看起来更好了, 不是吗?
It already looks better, huh?
又增加了几斤!
I've put on another kilo!
深呼吸. 合着的钢琴就像死了一样
Breathe in. A closed piano is a dead piano.
我卖活钢琴 活钢琴!
I sell live pianos, guys. Live ones!
看你的小牙齿 闪闪发光.
Look at all your little teeth sparkling away.
你得活跃起来...
You have to come alive...
...每一天. 做吧, 为了我
...today of all days. Do it, for my sake.
我确信你将会组成一个伟大的队伍
I'm sure you'll make a great team.
准备好了!你过来吗?
It's ready! Are you coming up?
是的, 我正在来. 我依赖你.
Yeah, I'm coming. I'm counting on you.
今天不要让她打扰我们
And let's not let her distract us today.
再见
See you later.
你知道, 亲爱的, 我们可以在厨房吃
You know, sweetheart, we could eat in the kitchen.
节食
Diet.
尝起来挺好
It tastes better like that.
-咖啡? -不, 我不能多喝.
-Coffee? -No, I mustn't overdo it.
我心满意足 我们会卖完钢琴
I'm on top of the world. We're going to sell out of pianos.
你似乎很自信
You seem pretty sure of that.
我不知道为什么. 只是有感觉
I can't explain why. It's a mind thing.
我不想被拒绝, 但今天是个散步的好日子
I don't want to be negative, but it's a nice day for a walk.
这个月我们已经赚了足够多的钱
We've got enough money for the month.
不是钱. 我想检验一个理论
It's not the money. I want to check on a theory.
所以我会花整个下午在收银台
So I'll spend the afternoon at the cash desk.
好的,我自己出去
Fine, I'll go out alone.
当然, 亲爱的, 不要烦恼. 太阳只是为你而散发光芒
Sure, honey, don't fret. The sun's shining just for you.
该死, 你浪费的时间对生命没有意义
Shit, the time you waste doing nothing with your life.
他们能把这做成个马戏表演
They could make a circus act out of this.
一个卖不出钢琴的钢琴推销员.
A piano seller who doesn't sell pianos.
这个世界以苦恼和荒谬为食
The world is fed on anguish and absurdity.
亲爱的, 你在和自己说话?
Sweetheart, are you talking to yourself?
我在浪费时间
I was messing around.
-我要出去. 一起来? -不，我不能离开钢琴.
-I'm going out. Coming? -No, I can't leave the pianos.
当我去卖香烟时，你能照看店铺吗？
Can you look after the shop while I run for some cigarettes?
-当然，我会照看 -你真是个天使
-Sure, I'll keep an eye on things. -You're an angel.
-生意怎么样 -糟糕，有点不景气
-How's business? -Bad. There's a recession on.
是的，但是没有新的
That's true, but there's nothing new about that.
给我来两个
Give me a couple of those.
我不相信 我只离开10分钟
I don't believe it. I only went out for 1 0 minutes!
对一个天才女店员足够了 记得戴贝雷帽的那个家伙吗？
Enough for a gifted salesgirl. Remember the guy in the beret?
戴贝雷帽的那个家伙，天哪！ 如今你不能相信任何人
The guy in the beret. Jesus! You can't trust anyone nowadays.
我不是卖它的人
I wasn't the one who sold it.
你是，由于你它被卖出了
You were. It was sold thanks to you.
是的，但仍然
Yeah, but still....
我们得庆祝一下 你想做什么？
We have to celebrate this. Anything you really want to do?
吃中国餐
Have a Chinese.
好的，我们去吃中国餐
Okay, fine, we'll go for a Chinese.
我要打你一顿，该死！
I'll tan your hide, damn it!
我真地烦了 他把自己锁在浴室里
I'm really fed up! He locked himself in the bathroom.
那个窗口太高了
And that window is so high!
我们为什么没有孩子？
Why do we ever have children?
-有什么问题？ -我有点晕，我做不了
-What's wrong? -I'm dizzy, I can't do it.
让我做
Let me do it.
小心
Be careful.
好的，继续，但要小心
Okay, go on, but watch out.
鲍勃!快点，来吧！
Bob! Hurry, come on!
来吧，你自己 让我头晕
Come on, yourself! Makes me dizzy!
你为什么做这个？
Archie! Why do you do this?
你父亲对你很愤怒
Your dad's mad at you.
鲍勃.他没事
He's okay, Bob.
我不相信！我会证明给你看，来吧
I don't believe it! I'll show you! Come on.
你留在这里直到干燥为止
I'll leave you here till you dry!
那是为了珍珠港 昨天...
That's for Pearl Harbour! Yesterday...
...他把自己关进电冰箱 把自己想象成为一个北极探险者
...he shut himself in the fridge. Fancied himself an Arctic explorer!
你个笨蛋！
You little moron!
下去，我会打开瓶子 请你饮杯酒
Go downstairs, I'll open up a bottle.
我坚持，你帮我一个忙。
I insist. You did me a favour.
亲爱的，他对你做了什么？
Darling, what did he do to you?
听说过三个超市女巫吗？
Ever hear about the three supermarket witches?
很好的故事，我会告诉你
A great story. I'll tell you.
坐下
Sit down.
他真的努力了
He's really going for it.
他们非常坚硬，他们都受伤了
They're so hard, they almost hurt.
摸一下，你会明白
Touch and you'll see.
来，摸
Go on, touch.
-感觉如何？ -非常硬
-Feel that? -Awfully hard.
他们受伤了
They hurt.
你得到了金鱼
You've got goldfish!
真的金鱼
Real goldfish!
怎么样？
How about some Pineau?
有什么可吃的吗？
Got anything to snack on?
在商店里请自便
Help yourself in the shop.
香蕉，椰子，杏
Bananas, coconuts, apricots.
不，都是甜的
No, that's all sweet.
我想要杏仁或花生
I want almonds or peanuts.
吃我的私处！吃！
Eat my pussy! Eat it!
快点
Hurry!
对不起，对不起
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
我不是使你兴奋？
I don't turn you on?
不是那个 有时我抵制我的欲望...
It's not that. Sometimes I resist my desires...
...为了感到我是自由的
...in order to feel I'm free.
-我烦了 -算了吧，我们去喝一杯
-I'm fed up! -Forget it. Let's go have a drink.
鲍勃已经一个月没有摸我了
Bob hasn't touched me for a month.
自从我离开门诊部
Not since I left the clinic.
等这么长时间正常吗？
Is it normal to have to wait so long?
一切会很顺利
It'll all work out.
是的
Yeah, right.
.有时当我们在床上，他会...
Sometimes when we're in bed, he'll...
...从后面进入...
...slip it in from behind...
...没有爱抚，如果我睡熟或...
...without caring if I'm asleep or....
我们去喝酒
Let's go have that drink.
金鱼喜欢那个曲调
The goldfish love that tune.
他们的是别的东西
That Pineau of theirs is something else.
太棒了，不是吗？
It's great, isn't it?
我们开业的那天 我们成功的卖出一架钢琴
The day we open, we manage to sell a piano.
一些卖钢琴，其他的
Some sell pianos, others Pineau.
-不是很棒吗？ -你太夸张了
-Isn't it great, though? -You're exaggerating.
我没有！你不认为卖出一架不是很棒吗？
No, I'm not! Don't you think it's great to sell one?
当然，但是你谈论它，好像有什么事发生在我们身上
Sure, but you talk about it as if something had happened to us.
有，我们卖了一架钢琴
It has, we sold a piano.
小心苹果
Mind my apple.
会是一个炎热的夜晚
It's going to be a hot night.
混蛋
The asshole.
在我看到我的名字印在书上之前，我会已经50岁了
I'll be 50 before I see my name in print.
他们都是混蛋！
They're all shitheads!
是的，你的运气现在没来
Yeah, your luck's not in right now.
我该把这些手稿送给你吗？
Shall I send the manuscript down to you?
没门，想想它惹的麻烦
No way. Think of the trouble it would cause.
把它寄给名单上的下一个人 名字在本上
Send it to the next on the list. The names are in the phone book.
钢琴卖得怎么样？
How are the pianos going?
很棒，我们昨天卖出第三架，毫不费力
Great. We sold the third yesterday. No sweat.
我得走了，她要来了，再见 埃迪
I have to go, she's coming in. See you, Eddy.
你在干什么？快点
What are you doing? Hurry up!
我已经很快了
I am hurrying.
这就是尼压住并强奸我的地方?
This is where you strangle me and rape me?
-最好首先强奸我 -好的
-Better rape me first. -All right.
听着
Look.
-看到那堵墙了吗？ -中国墙？
-See the little wall? -The Little Wall of China?
从湖边伸延过来的
The one that starts at the lake.
那个大岩石，看到了吗？
And that big rock, see?
-那个大东西？ -是的
-That big thing? -Yeah.
-真漂亮 -那个小房子不是也很好吗？
-Beautiful. -And isn't that little house nice?
你什么意思？
What are you getting at?
我喜欢这个地方
I love this fucking place.
你是对的，太完美了
You're right, it's perfect.
这地方的每件东西，太棒了
Everything in its place. Fantastic.
都是为你的，所有的！
It's all for you. All of it!
从墙开始，一直伸展到岩石外
It starts at the wall and goes beyond the rock.
房子在中间
And the house is in the middle.
不仅如此
And that's not all.
20岁生日快乐，亲爱的！
Happy 20th birthday, my love!
我们现在得进食
We'll have to eat it straightaway.
再来一口
Just one more drop.
看起来不可能
It doesn't seem possible.
听着，贝蒂，不要担心 仍何事都是可能的
Look, Betty, don't worry. All the papers are in order.
不，我想要买块地...
No, I mean to be able to buy a piece of land...
...有阳光，声音，所有的一切
...with its sunlight, its sounds and all that.
.当然，但是那就是你怎样在这看到的东西都是你的。
Sure, but that's how it is. Everything you see here is yours.
挂在树上的日落也是我的？
That sunset hanging in the trees is mine as well?
还有从山上溢出的寂静和微风？
And the silence and the breeze coming down the hill?
对，都是你的
Yes, it's all yours.
卖这个的家伙一定疯了
The guy who sold this must have been crazy.
这是我曾经得到过得最好的礼物
It's the best present I ever had.
我太高兴了
I'm so happy.
嘴唇也是我的？
Are these lips mine too?
那些眼睛也是我的？
Are those eyes mine?
他们也是你的。
They're yours too.
那也是我的？
Is that mine too?
所有的
All of it!
我梦到你的书出版了
I dreamed your book was published.
你为什么不想想其它的事？
Why don't you think of something else?
给我根香烟
Get me a cigarette.
-那些药是什么？ -没什么
-What are all these pills? -Nothing.
没什么？是安眠药吗？
Nothing? Are they sleeping pills?
我不是经常吃
I don't take them often.
算了
Forget it.
和我做爱
Make love to me.
菜都熟了
Good and ripe for a puree.
-还有什么 皮陈夫人 -火腿
-Anything else, Mrs. Pichon? -Ham.
-圆的还是方的 -圆的
-Round or square? -Round.
...你听说屠夫的妻子
Did you hear about the butcher's wife...
...和邮差私通吗？ 一点也不知道羞耻，两片？
...and the postman? No shame at all. Two slices?
四片
Four.
-鲍勃, 我陷入了困境
-Bob, I'm in the shit. -And I'm in the ham.
我必须送钢琴但送货工人没有来
I have a piano and my delivery men didn't show up.
钢琴必须送交
It has to be delivered.
你姊妹的丈夫有一辆卡车，是吗？
Your brother-in-law's got a truck, hasn't he?
太大了，是伐木卡车
It's too big, it's a logging truck.
我会应付，我有办法
I'll manage. I can drive those things.
所以没问题
So no problem!
安妮,来这
Annie, come here!
等一会，我打个电话
One second. I have a call to make.
告诉他我一会回来
Tell him I'll come back later.
好的，我会的
Okay, I'll do that.
嘿, 安妮,你怎么样？
Hi, Annie, how are you?
鲍勃近况好转吗?
Have things improved with Bob?
一点
A little.
为什么？
Why?
-你有什么心事? -思考使我精疲力尽
-You thinking of something? -Thinking exhausts me at the moment.
你真的是...
You really are...
...有趣的人
...a funny guy.
我怀疑
I doubt that.
25吨，它行吗？
Twenty-five tonnes. Think it'll do?
这东西一定值钱
This thing must be worth a bit.
富人才会买
Got to be rich to buy one of these.
别说了 知道怎么操作它吗？
Spare me your comments. Know how to work this?
只要按，很简单！
Just press, it's easy!
我能按吗？
Shall I press?
哦，该死，混蛋
Oh, shit! Asshole!
那是油擎，试按其他擎
That's the oil release, of course. It's the other one.
现在，小心
Now, watch.
-有说明书吗？ -是的，有
-Got a manual? -Yeah, there's a manual.
你们俩在玩什么？
What are you two playing at?
-你在做什么？ -我听不见
-What are you doing? -I can't hear!
下来
Bring it down.
多点
More.
你在玩什么？
What are you playing at?
你个混蛋！ 你知道它值多少钱吗？
You asshole! You know what this is worth?
你没有告诉我
You wouldn't tell me!
-混蛋！ -你认为我增加重量了？
-Fucking hell! -Do you think I've put on weight?
现在，你在我看来很好。
Right now, you look fine to me.
我认为我的胃有点胖
I think my belly's a bit fatter.
你们在说什么？
What are you talking about?
打电话给女伯爵，告诉她我们上路了，快点！
Call the countess to tell her we're on our way. Hurry up!
见鬼!
For chrissakes!
-左格,你来了吗？ -我正赶来
-Zorg, are you coming? -I'm coming!
-你拴住它了吗？ -夫人正在等着
-Did you tie it down? -Madame is waiting.
-我去 -我有些事要告诉你
-Let me go. -I have something to tell you.
-我等不及要告诉你 -我正在卖钢琴
-I can't wait to tell you. -I'm selling a piano!
我迟一个小时
I'm an hour late.
我就来
I'm coming!
那是什么？
What's that?
亚特兰蒂斯的灰尘
Dust from Atlantis?
验孕检测
It's a pregnancy test.
-它说什么？ -它说是
-And what does it say? -It says yes.
你用IUD怎会有孕？
But how, with your lUD?
有时发生
Happens sometimes.
不是真的
It can't be true.
坐下
Sit down.
我将回来照顾你，很棒，不是吗？
I'll be right back to look after you. It's great, huh?
有什么问题？你看起来很苍白
What's wrong? You look pale.
我们来得非常迟
We're late as hell.
从没看到过如此多的童车
Never saw so many baby carriages.
我们几乎做少了一个
That one nearly had it.
慢驶！卡车是全新的
Not so fast! The truck's brand-new!
我没开很快，它是滑轮引擎
I'm not going fast. Anyway, it's a turbo.
什么？你开玩笑？
What? Are you kidding?
仅仅25mph
I'm only doing 25 mph.
25？你开到了50
25? You're doing 50!
50，那不算快
50? That's not fast!
你确信你有驾照？
Are you sure you've got your licence?
我怀疑
I doubt it.
你怎么样？记得我吗？
How are you? Remember me?
在限速45mph的公路上，15吨车辆限速15mph...
Doing 60 with a truck limited to 45 mph...
...驾驶卡车速度超过60mph
...on a road limited to 1 5-tonne vehicles and to 30 mph.
不错，不错
Good start. Good start.
你的证件 彻底检查报告
Your papers. Full inspection, the whole lot.
对不起，我在做梦
Sorry, I was dreaming.
如果你没通过酒精检验，你会很快清醒
If you flunk the alcohol test, you'll wake up fast.
我方才发觉我将成为父亲
I just found out I'm going to be a daddy.
父亲
A father.
-香烟 -当然
-Got a cigarette? -Sure.
父亲是最后的伟大冒险
Fathers are the last great adventurers.
你会明白，有欢乐，但也有悲伤，悲伤
You'll see, there's joy, but sorrow too, sorrow.
浮岛，像沙漠中绿洲
A floating island, like a desert island.
-是的，亲爱的 -你？
-Yes, sweetheart. -And you?
再来一瓶香槟和雪糕
Another bottle of champagne and fritters.
-两人份的雪糕？ -是的，两人
-Fritters for two? -Yes, for two.
你将会吃三人份的
You'll eat for three.
我去小便
I'm going for a pee.
父亲真地是最后的伟大冒险？
Are fathers really the last great adventurers?
我看起来像是个冒险家吗？
And did I look like an adventurer?
对不起，我一直注意着你
Excuse me. I've been watching you.
我有些东西，你可能有兴趣
I've got something that may interest you.
不，谢谢，我没事
No, thanks, I'm fine.
-要白粉吗 -上等货色？
-There's a gram there. -Is it good?
-我不用它 -你不用它？
-I don't use it. -You don't use it?
它是补偿我的假期
It's to pay for my vacation.
我要去冲浪
I'm going surfing.
在夏威夷
In Hawaii.
那的巨浪 风吹拂你的秀发
Great waves out there. The wind in your hair.
-多少钱？ -1 500.
-How much? -1 500.
你确定？
Are you sure?
-你不要还给我 -合理价格，200
-I can take it back. -Hey, be reasonable. 200.
-没事 -付短裤的钱
-That's nothing. -It'll pay for a pair of shorts.
我会回来
I'll be back.
好吧？
Well?
冲浪运动员 只记得一件事：
Here, Mr. Surfer. Just remember one thing:
白色沙滩，夏威夷，巨浪，阳光
White sand, Hawaii, waves, sunshine.
太美了，但不是真的
It's beautiful, but it's not real.
血到处溅出
Blood is being spilled everywhere.
你为什么说那个？你疯了？
Why do you say that? Are you crazy?
哪些人为什么用光让我眼花缭乱？
Why were all those guys dazzling me with their lights?
-你没有开灯 -我真的喜欢蓝色，它太棒了
-You didn't have any lights on. -I really like blue. It's just great.
我没有开灯？ 天哪！一定是那些人搞错 了
I didn't have any lights on? Jesus, people can be really mean.
香槟酒通常让我清醒
Champagne usually wakes me up.
现在不要对我做那个 今晚不行
Don't do that to me now. Not tonight.
口渴？想喝点东西？
Thirsty? Want something to drink?
你没趣
You're not funny.
真的没趣
Really not funny.
玩拼字游戏，你喜欢的 我让你赢，好吗？
Let's play Scrabble. You love that. I'll let you win, okay?
你没趣 你总是让我孤单？
You're not funny. You going to leave me all alone?
你的包很难看
Your bag is ugly.
-那个小孩是谁？ -什么小孩？
-Who's that kid? -What kid?
-楼下的 -那是小尼古拉斯
-Downstairs. -That's little Nicolas.
他是个天才，但是他没有钢琴 这些都是什么？
He's a genius, but he hasn't got a piano. What's all this?
香殡！每人一瓶 还有西番莲果冰淇凌
Champagne! One bottle each. Petits fours and passion-fruit ice cream.
这是你的
And this is for you.
你绝不知道
You never know.
那些东西从不收缩
And those things never shrink.
我爱你
I love you.
它感觉像什么？
What does it feel like?
我不知道 我想再做一次检验来确定
I don't know. I want another test to be sure.
你喜欢这个主意吗？
Do you like the idea?
我还没想过
I haven't thought about it.
但我说它不坏
But I'd say it's not so bad.
作为给你的礼物
As a present to you.
我们做爱
We made love.
我有的飘飘若仙的感觉
I had a dizzy sensation.
当我们做爱时，她的IUD就像门一样被风撞破
While we screwed, her IUD was like a broken door banging in the wind.
验孕测试： 阴性
PREGNANC Y DlAGNOSlS: NEGATlVE.
她可能会一时想不开
Mine is in heat, yours is going bananas.
不要说那个
Don't ever say that.
对不起
Sorry.
你看到埃迪和利萨难道不高兴吗？
Aren't you glad to see Eddy and Lisa again?
还有秃头？
And Rusty?
即使你是秃顶，我也爱你
I'd love you even if you were bald.
我命运坎坷
Life's got it in for me.
一旦我想要某些东西，我总不能获取
As soon as I want something, I realise I can't have it.
我甚至不能有个孩子
I can't even have a baby.
有什么问题？
What's wrong?
你的头发看起来很好
Your hair looks good like this.
你应该游会泳，水不热不冷
You should swim a bit. The water's lovely.
怎么样，亲爱的？
How about it, honey?
你疯了
You're crazy!
我看着鱼杆
Watch the float, and that's all there is to it.
我不会做爱
I don't give a fuck.
我不想激怒你，但是你看到贝蒂的状况了吗？
I don't want to piss you off, but have you seen the state Betty's in?
她一脸死灰
She's lost all her colour.
她一直咬嘴唇，看星星
She keeps on biting her lips and looking at the stars.
你比鱼还不如
Fuck, you're worse than a fish.
我能做些事来帮助他们吗？
Can I do anything to help you guys out?
她认为她怀孕了
She thought she was pregnant.
不是每次都有效，试一下
Well, it can't work every time. Try again.
我有感觉，贝蒂想要不存在的东西
I get the feeling that Betty wants something that doesn't exist.
这个世界对她来说太小了
The world's too fucking small for her.
你不会像那样帮助她
You won't help her like that.
该死，埃迪，我得救她
Fuck, Eddy, I've got to save her.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我的贝蒂，回来
My Betty. Come back.
是我
It's me.
我听到声音
I hear voices.
不，那是风
No, that's the wind.
一些怪人总是在早上3点打开收音机，等待第三次世界大战
And some nut always has a radio on at 3 a.m., waiting for World War lll.
我在我的脑袋里听到这声音
I hear the voices in my head.
我要疯了
I'm going insane.
在我的脑袋里
In my head.
现在都结束了
It's all over now.
"当加恩斯把钉子钉进西维的身体...
"Whenever Josiane dug her nails into Sylvie's body...
...捏她的胸部...
...kneaded her breasts or greedily tongued her hairy pussy...
...他回想起罗杰
...she'd think of Roger.
她想要他带走她 残酷的刺穿她的内心
She wanted him to take her, brutally penetrate her core.
她考虑刺穿那个该死的地方
She'd think of his stiff pole pounding into her gaping pussy.
'天呀，真有趣!"'
'Jesus, Jesus, the joy of it!"'
我不想尝试任何事
I won't try anything.
我不想受伤
I don't want to get hurt.
不要太紧张
Don't be so uptight.
你得鼓起勇气试这个
Oh, wow! You've got one hell of a nerve trying this.
我钦羡你
I admire you.
如果你想要，我有个热水瓶 你自便
I have a thermos flask if you want. Help yourself.
你的名字是什么？
What's your name?
我只想知道你的名字 我发誓不会告诉其他人
I just want to know your name. I swear I won't tell anyone.
如果你解开我，我会帮助你
If you untie me, I can help you.
我会把枪对准那混蛋们 我不喜欢这工作
I could turn a gun on the bastards. I hate this job.
你为什么不告诉我你的名字？相信我
Why won't you tell me your name? Trust me.
小心那个胖家伙  乔治
Watch out for the fat one, Georges-Alain.
小心，他是个卑鄙的人
Be careful, he's a real shit.
他会不发警告就开枪 他以前杀死过旅客，我会杀了他
He'll fire without warning. He's shot passersby before now. I'd kill him.
他会找到你
He'll get you.
我愿意看你
I'd like to watch you.
拿我做人质 我们会像邦妮和克莱德
Take me hostage. We'll be like Bonnie and Clyde.
你全错了
You've got it all wrong, shithead.
当你的妻子晚上头疼时 你想和她做爱...
When your wife has a headache the night you want to screw her...
...告诉她你不是在寻找她的灵魂
...tell her it's not her head you're after!
你不了解我的妻子
You don't know my wife.
她就像其它的女人
She's like any other woman.
他们都是一样的 都是婊子，每个
They're all the same, all bitches, every last one.
听着，当你月底把工资带回家...
Look, when you bring your pay home at the end of the month...
...那么她不想要阿斯匹林
...she doesn't want an aspirin then.
拿着钱
Take the money.
你个婊子
You fucking bitch!
,当我抓住你 我会让你亲我的XX
When I catch up with you, I'll make you suck my dick!
你在那做什么，贝蒂？
What are you doing here, Betty?
你在做什么？ 我一直在找你
What are you doing? I've been looking all over for you.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
如果我死了 我愿意让人们来看我
If I was dead, I'd like people to come to see me.
你在说什么？ 快点
What are you talking about? Come on.
想看我下午找到的东西吗？
Want to see what I found this afternoon?
干什么用的？
What's it for?
任何你想要的东西，贝蒂
Anything you want, Betty.
一个岛
An island.
你疯了
You're crazy.
放回原处
Put that back. It's not nice.
戴上
Put them on. Put them on, please. Put them on.
如果任何人问我今天做了什么...
If anyone ever asks what I did today...
...告诉他们我们整天在一起
...tell them we were together all day.
是的，我甚至和一个漂亮的浅黑肤色的女人做爱
Yes. I even screwed a beautiful brunette.
漂亮，真的漂亮
Beautiful. Really beautiful.
我们明天去海边
We'll go to the seaside tomorrow.
好吗？
Is it good?
是个好主意，是吗？
This was a good idea, huh?
我会为你买艘船，好吗？
I'll buy you a boat, okay?
该死，太困难了，不是吗？
Shit, it's been tough, huh?
某个地方一定有你和我的天堂
There must be a paradise somewhere for you and me.
再来个冰淇淋？
Want another ice cream?
我现在会去
I'll go and get it now or we'll be here ages.
那个和你在一起的女孩 抢走了我的孩子
Hey, that girl who was with you has gone off with my little boy.
那个和你在一起的女孩 穿着短衣的人
That girl who was with you. The one in the short dress.
拦下他
Stop him!
现在已停止营业了 对不起，先生，商店关门了
This floor is closed to the public. I'm sorry, sir. The store is closed.
你什么意思？ 只要一会
What do you mean? It'll only take a minute.
不会太长！贝蒂
It won't take long! Betty!
整层都被租出去了
This whole floor has been hired.
我想要架钢琴 我想为我的妻子和孩子来架钢琴
I want a piano. I want a piano for my wife and kid.
我完全理解了，但是现在---
I fully understand, but right now--
-多少钱？ -我不知道，我们关门了
-How much? -I don't know. We're closed.
求你了，那个顾客是我的妻子！ 她在哪里？
For fuck's sake, that customer is my wife! Where is she?
在帐篷里，她不想被打扰 她说的，先生
In the tepee. She doesn't want to be disturbed. She paid, sir.
贝蒂，你在这在干什么？
Betty, what are you doing in here?
过来
Come and sit down with us.
-你是谁？ -他是我生命中的男人
-Who are you? -He's the man of my life.
他的母亲一直在找他 我们得离开这
His mother's been looking for him. We've got to get out of here.
和我们一起
Come with us.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
来吧
Come on.
抓住他，他的母亲正在赶来 快点，贝蒂！
Keep him, his mother's on her way. Quick, Betty!
-我不能，没用 -跑，否则他们会分开我们
-I can't. It's no use. -Run or they'll part us.
他们不能分开我们 我们互相需要
They can't part us. We were meant for each other.
快点，贝蒂，快点
Hurry, Betty, hurry.
-不要慌张！ -发生什么事了？
-Don't panic! -What happened?
-请坐下 -贝蒂在哪？
-Please sit down. -Where's Betty?
呆在这！
Stay here!
-该死，我不相信 -不要呆在这
-Fuck, I don't believe it. -Don't stay here.
鲍勃,发生什么了？
Bob, what happened?
她戳出一只眼
She poked an eye out.
-我不相信 -她看起来糟糕，但她活着
-I don't believe it! -She looks bad, but she's alive.
坐下，我会去问 坐下
Go and sit down. I'll go and ask. Just sit down.
在这等我
Wait for me here.
-好吗？ -她没事，她正在睡觉
-Well? -She's okay, she's sleeping.
-我能看她吗？ -是的，但你得填下表
-Can I see her? -Yes, but you have to fill out forms.
只是手续 但必须得做
It's just a formality, but it has to be done.
我会让你去的
I'll put you through.
他是这种人....
He's the one who....
-你是丈夫吗？ -不
-Are you the husband? -No.
亲戚？
A relative?
不，我只是其他人
No, I'm all the rest.
我们生活在一起 所以我能填出那些东西
We live together, so I can fill those things out.
你有她的身份卡吗？
Do you have her identity card?
-我到底在哪填？ -这
-Where the hell did I put it? -Here.
照片上她很可爱，不是吗？
It's a nice photo, huh?
-她的社会保险号？ -我不知道
-Her social security number? -I don't know it.
多么痛苦
What a pain.
没事，没事
Okay, that's fine.
你能离开了，鲍勃 我想独自看她
You can go, Bob. I want to see her alone.
-你别过于悲伤 -是的
-Can you drive back? -Yes.
对不起，这是10号房间吗？
Excuse me, is this room 1 0?
刺自己眼睛的女孩？ 她很稳定，但需要休息
The girl who poked her eye out? She's stable but needs rest.
-我能看她吗？ -拜访时间已经结束了
-Can I see her? -Visiting hours are over.
-只要五分钟 -好吧，那么，时间不要太长
-Just five minutes. -All right, then, but not for long.
不超过五分钟
No more than five minutes.
来吧
Come on.
呆在这也没用
There's no point in staying.
我只想再呆点时间
I want to stay just a bit longer.
明天下午之前，她不会醒
She won't wake before noon tomorrow.
她服镇静剂了
She's sedated.
来吧 你能明天再来
Come on. You can come back tomorrow.
她那时状况会更好
She'll be better then.
-我受够了 -你对其他人没有尊重
-I've had enough! -You have no respect for others.
你能谈论尊重！ ...当你送货给
You can talk about respect! What do you get up to...
...顾客时，你做了什么？
...when you deliver to your lonely customers?
-你个混蛋，你在利用我！ -不要破坏我的墙
-You bastard, you're using me! -Stop busting my balls!
胡扯!
Shithead!
你疯了
You're totally crazy to get this wound up over nothing.
没事，你对我不忠 你称那为没事？
Nothing? You cheat on me and you call that nothing?
你对我不忠，不让我走 至少让我走
You cheat on me and don't fuck me! At least fuck me!
你不知道你在说什么！
You don't know what you're saying!
我对吵架感到烦了
I've had enough of this row.
这不是吵架
This isn't a row. You have to be in love for a row.
是的，说
Yes, speaking.
谁？
Who?
什么？你读了？
What? You've read it?
不，我相信你，我只是有点惊奇
No, I believe you. I'm just surprised.
它还没来
It hasn't come yet.
好的，我每页都会签字
Okay, I'll sign every page.
我想要15%
I want 15%.
好的，10%，我不会让步
Okay, 10%. I don't give a shit.
不，我现在不能出门
No, I can't travel now.
是的，我正在写另一本书...
Yes, I'm doing another one...
...但我不能解释 只是突然出现在脑中的东西
...but I can't explain. Just stuff that pops into mind.
贝蒂，我们成功了 书会出版了
Betty, we did it! The book's going to be published!
他们对你做了什么？
What have they done to you?
混蛋
The bastards!
我们会成功的，亲爱的
We're going to make it, my love.
我在写另一本书
I'm writing another book.
为了你
For you.
为了你，贝蒂
For you, Betty.
献给你
Dedicated to you.
你在这做什么？
What are you doing here?
-你对她做了什么？ -你疯了！出去！
-What did you do to her? -You're crazy! Get out!
这些都是什么？ 我想看她的医生
What is all this shit? I want to see her doctor.
这些是什么？告诉我
What is this shit? Tell me!
坐下
Sit down.
我想看你
I wanted to see you.
她出于震惊的状态
She's in a state of shock.
知道那是什么意思吗？
Know what that means?
严肃地说 我们预测不了结果
It is serious. We can't predict the outcome.
我们不能保证她会痊愈
We can't guarantee that she'll ever recover.
勇敢点，老人
Be brave, old man.
现代化学突飞猛进
Chemistry has made great strides.
电疗法有成效了
Electrotherapy gets results.
不要听他们说的废话
Don't listen to all the crap they say about this.
-我要带她回家 -听我说，那个女孩神志不清
-I'm taking her home. -Listen to me. That girl is insane.
-完全疯了 -闭嘴，闭嘴，求你了
-Totally insane. -Shut up, shut up, please.
是你的药把她弄疯的
It's your medicine that drove her mad!
你的东西破坏了她的精神
Your shit's wrecking her mind!
你在让她不舒服！
You're making her sick!
我说逃走！迷路了！
I said beat it! Get lost!
-我操！-算了吧！
-I'll slug you! -Forget it!
我在这个房子里一直听到你的声音，贝蒂
I keep hearing your voice in the house, Betty.
最糟糕的是，寂静...
Worst of all, the silence...
...话语突然出现：
...and words that just pop up:
"我找不到该死的糖!"
"I can't find the fucking sugar!"
"你开玩笑."
"You're kidding."
"那令人讨厌的真空吸尘器!"
"That shitty vacuum cleaner!"
"左格, 你睡着了吗?"
"Zorg, are you asleep?"
我们一起出发度蜜月
We're going away together.
尽最后努力
Make one last effort.
我们是天作之合
We were meant for each other.
没人能分开我们，没有人
No one can ever separate us, no one, ever.
你在写吗？
Are you writing?
不，我只是在想
No, I was just thinking.